employmentnigeria.com 2014-09-28

# Employment Nigeria

**_Posted:_** _June 6, 201_ 1 

**Overview**  
Employment Nigeria (“Employmentng.com”) knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. This policy describes the types of information collected, how it may and may not be used, and how it is protected. By visiting Employmentng.com’s website ("Website"), or using any of our services on the website ("Website Services"), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy and our use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collected From Users**  
In the course of your browsing the Website, Employmentng.com may collect the IP address of the computer through which your visit is enabled; cookie information; information regarding the pages, links, banners, icons and other parts of the Website that are accessed or clicked on during a visit to the Website; information regarding the date, time, and duration of your visit; and information you may volunteer, e.g., in response to survey requests or as part of a registration. Upon any registration for, and in subsequent interaction with, Website Services, Employmentng.com may collect mandatory information such as your User Name, Password, primary email address, etc. A "cookie" is a small line of text that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer when you visit a website. Employmentng.com uses a cookie for record-keeping and verification purposes and a cookie helps us provide better service to you. For example, we use a cookie to verify your session and user identification and to track the pages within the Website that you visited. Your browser should have options to accept, reject or provide you with a notice when a cookie is sent. However, if you disable cookies, you may not be able to use the Website Services. Please note that Employmentng.com does not and cannot read cookies set by other websites.

**Use of Information Collected**  
We use the information we collect to provide our services and features to you, to measure and improve those services and features, and to provide you with customized user experience. We may contact you with service-related announcements from time to time. Your information will not be shared with any third parties except as explained below.

As part of our business, we may pass to our service partners aggregated information (data gathered up across multiple or all user accounts) regarding visitors, users, and historical transactions in a manner that will not personally identify any individual user. We may aggregate personal information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally.

We will not sell, rent or transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to any third party, unless we are required by law, court order or regulation, or we believe that disclosure is necessary to comply with law or legal process, or to cooperate with local or federal authorities, or to protect or defend against fraud, misuse of the Employmentng.com Website, breach of any of your obligations hereunder, or to protect our intellectual property rights. In addition, we may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information in connection with a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or substantially all of the assets of Employmentng.com to another company (an "Acquirer Company"), provided that such Personally Identifiable Information shall only be used by the Acquirer Company in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Employmentng.com will not track your Internet usage outside of the confines of the Employmentng.com Website.

**Your obligations to other Users**  
As a User, you have certain obligations to other Users. Some of these obligations are imposed by applicable law and regulations, and others have become commonplace in user-friendly communities of like-minded members. Do not abuse the Employmentng.com service by using it to spam, abuse, harass, or otherwise violate this Privacy Policy. You must not download or otherwise disseminate any information that may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, or which may otherwise violate the purpose and spirit of Employmentng.com and its community of Users. 

**Information security**  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, so you do so at your own risk. We restrict access to personal information to employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf.

**Third Party Sites**  
Employmentng.com does not control the privacy policies of third party sites or service providers to which we provide links. These third party sites or service providers may use cookies to provide a service or serve ads based on a user's prior visits to Employmentng.com. Please be aware that if you click on an ad or third party link, you will be subject to the third party's privacy policy.

**Changes to the Employmentng.com Privacy Policy**  
You agree that Employmentng.com may amend this policy from time to time by posting the revised Privacy Policy on this Website. Your continued use of any portion of the Website or Employmentng.com service following the posting of the revised policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

**How to contact us**  
You can contact Employmentng.com by sending an email to [info@employmentng.com](mailto:support@employmentng.com)

ADVERTISEMENT

Site Activity Feed

eddypure a Job Seeker Joined **Employment Nigeria**
